Summit of the Americas Collection 2001.0037
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Summit of the Americas Collection
1998-2001
2001.0037
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
1.0 Linear feet
The Summit of the Americas was held in Quebec City, Quebec, in April 2001. The collection consists of ephemera related to the Summit.
King, George, IV [collector].
History
The Summit of the Americas was held in Quebec City, Quebec, in April 2001.
Scope and Content
The collection includes publications, flyers, periodicals and a poster protesting the goals of the summit meeting.
Arrangement
Materials were filed according to size.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to Archives & Special Collections by Mr. King in May 2001.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials documenting activities of organizations and individuals considered "alternative" to the mainstream of American culture, politics, society, and lifestyle. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Fliers. [printed matter]; Photographs.; Posters.; Publications.
- Series I: Collection, 1998-2001
  - Fliers, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Periodicals (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Les Anarchistes, 2001
    - Autres voix, 2001
    - Contre le Sommet des Amériques, 2001
    - L'Exemplaire, V. IX, #22, April 18, 2001
    - L'info Bourg, V. 15, # 4, April, 2001
    - Non à la ZLÉA (2 publications), undated
    - Stop the FTAA!, undated
    - Voices Outside the Wall, 2001 April
    - Voir, #460, 19-25 April, 2001
  - Poster, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)